<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <copyright>Copyright (c) 2021 Verizon Media. All rights reserved.</copyright>
        <description>Latest Financial News for AAPL</description>
        <image>
            <height>45</height>
            <link>http://finance.yahoo.com/q/h?s=AAPL</link>
            <title>Yahoo! Finance: AAPL News</title>
            <url>https://s.yimg.com/rz/stage/p/yahoo_finance_en-US_h_p_finance_2.png</url>
            <width>144</width>
        </image>
        <item>
            <description>Coming out of the dot-com bubble, very few people would have guessed that 20 years later the
                five largest companies in the U.S. would all be technology companies. Granted, technology companies are
                not known for high dividend yields, but their cash-flow-rich business models have supported years of
                dividend increases. Let's take a closer look at three tech companies that should get more love from
                dividend investors.
            </description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">43eca413-5a77-3a2d-a0dc-52cfd0249a9b</guid>
            <link>
                https://finance.yahoo.com/m/43eca413-5a77-3a2d-a0dc-52cfd0249a9b/3-underrated-tech-dividend.html?.tsrc=rss
            </link>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 13:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>3 Underrated Tech Dividend Stocks You Shouldn't Ignore</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>Roku and Etsy beat earnings, but sold off late. In a mixed market, AMD and Robinhood soared,
                signaling a meme stock shift.
            </description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">752d747e-3368-3733-8aa9-72646c5c2abc</guid>
            <link>
                https://finance.yahoo.com/m/752d747e-3368-3733-8aa9-72646c5c2abc/dow-jones-futures%3A-roku%2C-etsy.html?.tsrc=rss
            </link>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 12:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Dow Jones Futures: Roku, Etsy Dive On Earnings; AMD, Robinhood Signal Meme Stock Shift</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>A senior Apple engineer has claimed she has been placed on administrative leave after raising
                concerns about sexism and health and safety failings in the office.
            </description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c1a35f96-bd00-3324-a08e-815522a08a66</guid>
            <link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-worker-complained-sexism-hostile-120809753.html?.tsrc=rss
            </link>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 12:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Apple worker who complained about sexism and 'hostile' workplace put on paid leave</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>These hugely profitable businesses have plenty of room to make some aggressive increases to
                their dividends in the future.
            </description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">66170691-21f5-3ff8-a26e-7129c6f9becc</guid>
            <link>
                https://finance.yahoo.com/m/66170691-21f5-3ff8-a26e-7129c6f9becc/3-dividend-stocks-that-could.html?.tsrc=rss
            </link>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>3 Dividend Stocks That Could Double Their Payouts in 5 Years</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>Former Washington Post Executive Editor, Marty Baron, joins 'Influencers with Andy Serwer' to
                discuss his experience working under Amazon Founder Jeff Bezos.
            </description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bd81db50-0d01-3aa1-b149-0ed01bde25be</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/jeff-bezos-helped-washington-post-110000282.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Jeff Bezos helped the Washington Post ‘take advantage of the gift the internet had to offer: Marty
                Baron
            </title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>In this episode of Influencers, Andy is joined by legendary journalist &amp; former Washington
                Post Executive Editor, Marty Baron, for a discussion on the state of the media industry, his experience
                covering the Trump administration, and why he decided to walk away from the news business.
            </description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5788ea0b-d2b3-3e06-8367-8b1885116302</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/influencers-andy-serwer-marty-baron-100000980.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Influencers with Andy Serwer: Marty Baron</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>(Bloomberg) -- TikTok-owner ByteDance Ltd. has laid off hundreds of employees as the social
                giant shuts down a significant part of its online education businesses to comply with Beijing’s new
                regulatory regime for the after-school tutoring industry.The Beijing-based company told employees
                working on edtech products including Guagua Long, Qingbei and GoGoKid that they will be laid off with
                compensation, said a person familiar with the matter. At least hundreds of employees were affected,
                while ot
            </description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">45f2fa52-a951-3f93-922a-845b4f8f6c50</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bytedance-lays-off-hundreds-china-094516284.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 09:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>ByteDance Lays Off Hundreds After China’s Tutoring Crackdown</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>AAPL is hovering near record highs</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cca72c22-2e15-3cc0-993b-c3e3a45a0c86</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-stock-best-faang-name-185240154.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 18:52:40 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Apple Stock is the Best FAANG Name to Own This Month</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>The online Apple Store has undergone a redesign, after mysteriously going offline. Ordinarily,
                the Apple Store is taken offline for the launch of new products. It tends to go down shortly before
                Apple’s major events, apparently to give the infrastructure underpinning it time to be updated for any
                new releases.
            </description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">51f20c24-c5d4-3996-bb2f-493e4e59f262</guid>
            <link>
                https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/apple-store-website-buy-iphone-mac-ipad-b1896748.html?.tsrc=rss
            </link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Apple Store website gets redesign after going offline</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>A Relative Strength Rating upgrade for Apple shows improving technical performance. Will it
                continue?
            </description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9d1f0d7c-da6d-374f-8ae0-af2c9fff9637</guid>
            <link>
                https://finance.yahoo.com/m/9d1f0d7c-da6d-374f-8ae0-af2c9fff9637/apple-earns-ibd-relative.html?.tsrc=rss
            </link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Apple Earns IBD Relative Strength Rating Upgrade, Hitting 70+</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>Apple Inc is working with more Chinese suppliers to produce its latest iPhones, Japan's Nikkei
                newspaper said on Wednesday, as a tech feud stemming from a trade war with the United States prompts
                Beijing to strengthen domestic firms. The iPhone maker has warned of supply shortages as the U.S.-China
                trade tensions and the coronavirus pandemic have intensified pressure on global supply chains. Beijing
                is also strengthening efforts to create world-leading local tech firms, with apparently
                government-supported Chinese firms working to manufacture products for global firms including Apple.
            </description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">951d0723-0e7a-3980-89eb-4f53fb3d243e</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/1-apple-works-chinese-suppliers-141703093.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 14:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>UPDATE 1-Apple works with Chinese suppliers for latest iPhones - Nikkei</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>(Bloomberg) -- While much of Corporate America scrambled to adjust Covid-19 policies this
                summer in response to a surge of cases, Amazon.com Inc. was dismantling its coronavirus testing sites.
                Sequestered corners of warehouses and conference rooms where, just a few weeks ago employees were
                performing nasal swabs, are now blocked off or cleared of equipment.This may seem counterintuitive as
                the delta variant rips through many of the states where Amazon has warehouses. But the company says
                employe
            </description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2a408f99-a454-35ac-9788-04046e7031de</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-covid-dilemma-mandate-vaccinations-140030043.html?.tsrc=rss
            </link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 14:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Amazon’s Covid Dilemma: Mandate Vaccinations and Risk Losing Workers</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>Sonu Kalra, who manages the Fidelity Blue Chip Growth fund, invests in companies whose products
                or services customers can’t live without. That has led to holdings like Amazon.com, Apple, and Alphabet.
            </description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8ec9ace1-a5d3-33f2-8f7e-92373d26cd12</guid>
            <link>
                https://finance.yahoo.com/m/8ec9ace1-a5d3-33f2-8f7e-92373d26cd12/why-this-%2457b-fund-loves.html?.tsrc=rss
            </link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Why This $57B Fund Loves Amazon, Apple, and Lyft Stock</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>The global chip shortage started in 2018 and 2019 as escalating trade conflicts disrupted
                semiconductor supply chains, then worsened in 2020 as the pandemic exacerbated those disruptions. Many
                top chipmakers and analysts expect the ongoing crisis to last through 2023. Let's examine five main
                aspects of the chip shortage -- and how they could affect certain sectors and stocks.
            </description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cb5252d3-9155-37ec-9d3c-6503298b1136</guid>
            <link>
                https://finance.yahoo.com/m/cb5252d3-9155-37ec-9d3c-6503298b1136/tech-companies-are-facing-a.html?.tsrc=rss
            </link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Tech Companies Are Facing a Global Chip Shortage: 5 Tips for Investors</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) had some interesting twists this year, and the company might be making
                the right moves, further pushing growth capacity. We will analyze their approach towards competitors,
                new products and overall stock performance.
            </description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d40f1f85-e186-322f-889a-d72c892c5519</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/yes-apple-nasdaq-aapl-still-104323377.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 10:43:23 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Yes, Apple (NASDAQ:AAPL) Can Still Grow, Here's How</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>Memory-chip maker Micron Technology (NASDAQ: MU) just announced a quarterly dividend policy.
                The payouts are starting out small, but I expect the company to build up its dividend yield over time.
                Let's see what Micron's payouts will mean to us shareholders.
            </description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bfe8bc50-4c41-37af-afc9-370dabc0b9e7</guid>
            <link>
                https://finance.yahoo.com/m/bfe8bc50-4c41-37af-afc9-370dabc0b9e7/will-micron-technology%27s-new.html?.tsrc=rss
            </link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 10:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Will Micron Technology's New Dividend Policy Pay Dividends For Investors?</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>Former Washington Post Executive Editor, Marty Baron, joins 'Influencers with Andy Serwer' to
                discuss President Trump's disproven claims about 2020 election fraud. 
            </description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5867d71c-abc9-39c5-810a-f5e12c0fe7a5</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/election-fraud-claims-fiasco-democracy-100000899.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Election fraud claims are 'a fiasco for our democracy': Marty Baron</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>Affirm stock extends gains on reports that Apple plans to partner with Canadian PayBright unit
                on a 'buy now, pay later' program for Apple device purchases.
            </description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bc44c5b1-721d-3621-a4b3-389a287eb2ae</guid>
            <link>
                https://finance.yahoo.com/m/bc44c5b1-721d-3621-a4b3-389a287eb2ae/affirm-stock-extends-gains-on.html?.tsrc=rss
            </link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 06:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Affirm Stock Extends Gains on 'Buy Now Pay Later' Deal With Apple Canada</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>The iPhone maker has warned of supply shortages as the U.S.-China trade tensions and the
                coronavirus pandemic have intensified pressure on global supply chains. Beijing is also strengthening
                efforts to create world-leading local tech firms, with apparently government-supported Chinese firms
                working to manufacture products for global firms including Apple. According to the Nikkei report,
                China's Luxshare Precision Industry Co Ltd is set to build up to 3% of the iPhone 13 series, Lens Tech
                Co Ltd will supply metal casings and Sunny Optical Tech Group Co Ltd will supply rear camera lenses.
            </description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d207448d-8ebf-3c78-b363-3d69db25df42</guid>
            <link>https://in.finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-works-chinese-suppliers-latest-045155638.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 04:51:55 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Apple works with Chinese suppliers for latest iPhones - Nikkei</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>An already busy week in the buy-now, pay-later (BNPL) market got even busier Tuesday after a
                report indicated that Apple Inc. plans to work with Affirm Holdings Inc. on an installment offering for
                those looking to buy various Apple devices in Canada.
            </description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c7e4f725-f7b6-3ae3-9721-cb5d2874e1a1</guid>
            <link>
                https://finance.yahoo.com/m/c7e4f725-f7b6-3ae3-9721-cb5d2874e1a1/affirm-stock-rallies-after.html?.tsrc=rss
            </link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 23:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Affirm stock rallies after report of plans to work with Apple in Canada</title>
        </item>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 14:03:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <link>http://finance.yahoo.com/q/h?s=AAPL</link>
        <title>Yahoo! Finance: AAPL News</title>
    </channel>
</rss>
